couponlawn.com 2019-06-19

# Privacy Policy - Coupon Lawn

**Personal information types that we collect**

We collect personal information such as contact details, relationship details, transaction details and location details in order to provide our services with less hassle. They will assist us to know your requirements and provide a betters service.

 **How we collect your information**

We collect your information through sign up forms, account details and subscriptions. For instance, you will be asked to provide your information in order to access specific services. The transaction details are gathered by tracking coupons and through communication methods. We also acquire personal information from third parties time to time.

 **How we use your personal information**

We use your personal information to provide our products or services, evaluate the types of coupons that you are interested, fulfil your requirements, provide advertisements, send reminders, assist you to advertise for jobs and manage our day to day business.

 **When and why we will disclose your personal information**

We may share your personal information with affiliate companies, our service providers, merchants and trusted business partners. If we not share them with other external parties without your consent.

 **Information related to cookies**

When you are interacting with our website, we will collect your information through digital means, such as cookies, browser analysis tools, web server logs, web beacons and pixel tags. This information will be used to record your interactivity with our services and fulfill your requirements.

 **The choices you have**

We provide a variety of services for your convenience. For example, you can manage your email preferences by logging into the community, manage how your browser handle cookies and control how your personal information is getting interacted with the website. You can also change the social media sharing settings by visiting the Apps tab from your social media profile.

http://CouponLawn.com usually accepts industry preferred standards in order to protect all your precious information. For example, we continuously monitor our systems and take necessary measures to stay away from vulnerable attacks. Since we use a tier one access data center, your information will not be sent through the internet or through any other storage method, which are vulnerable to attacks. However, we cannot assure that your information will not be deleted or altered by any of our physical or technical safeguards.

 **Accessing your personal information**

By keeping your personal information in our databases, we will be able to provide the best coupons to you through our business partners and merchants. Therefore, you are encouraged to provide real information and keep them updates for the convenience of both parties.

 **Special notice to the users who live outside of Canada**

The headquarters of CouponLawn.com is located in Canada. Therefore, your personal information will be accessed and transferred to Canada or to the affiliates, business partners, service providers or merchants who live all around the world. Your information will also be accessed upon request by government law enforcement officials or national security authorities of Canada. However, we have taken necessary steps to protect your privacy and keep the personal information safe according to our privacy policy.

 **Privacy practices related to third parties**

This privacy policy only addressed the disclosure and you of information by CouponLawn.com through your interaction with the services. All the other websites which you can access through our website will have their own privacy policies. In addition, our business partners and affiliates also have their own privacy policy. Therefore, you are recommended to go through the respective pages as well, in order to stay away from hassle.

 **Information related to communities.**

In our services, you will be able to find communities and several other areas which ask you to provide your personal information. They might also ask you to communicate with fellow members, post product reviews and submit media content. Before you go to do any interaction in those places, you should read our Terms of Use page carefully. Everything you post on those websites can be accessed by anyone. All the personal information can be read, collected and be used by others for many activities and such activities are beyond our control. For instance, when you post your email address along with a comment, explaining how to redeem a coupon, there will be a chance of getting your email address into the hands of spammers. Then you will receive a large number of spam messages from external parties. Therefore, all the users are advised to stay away from posting their personal information on third party websites. If you have any doubt regarding this, you can always contact us through the customer support service.

We might update our privacy policy from time to time in order to keep the clients stay updates about our new products and services. Once we make a modification in the privacy policy, we will let you know about it through an email. The email will be sent to the address that you used when creating the account. Therefore, we encourage all our visitors to keep themselves updated with this page and be active on emails, in order to enjoy a continuous service.

 **Policy regarding children below 18 years of age.**

Children who have not yet completed 18 years of age are strictly prohibited to use the services of CouponLawn.com. All our services are specifically designed for the use of adults. By using our services, you indicate that you are at least 18 years old. If we recognize any account that violate out terms and conditions, we will take measures to delete that account without any prior notice.
